 
 {
  "savoir_ses_tables": [
  
    {
      "id": "q1",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 x 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "42"
    },
    {
      "id": "q2",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "id": "q3",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "12 - 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": "q4",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 + 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "id": "q5",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "72 : 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q6",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 : 1 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q7",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 + 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "id": "q8",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "48 : 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q9",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "0 : 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": "q10",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "72 : 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q11",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "42 : 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q12",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "11 - 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": "q13",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "11 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "q14",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "10 - 4 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q15",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 + 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "id": "q16",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 x 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "id": "q17",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "54 : 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q18",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "11 - 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": "q19",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 x 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "id": "q20",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 + 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "id": "q21",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "17 - 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q22",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "id": "q23",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 x 0 =",
      "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": "q24",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "12 - 3 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q25",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 + 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "id": "q26",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "11 - 4 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q27",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "0 : 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": "q28",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "11 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": "q29",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "56 : 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q30",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "18 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "id": "q31",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 + 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "id": "q32",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 x 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "81"
    },
    {
      "id": "q33",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "14 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q34",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "13 - 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q35",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "16 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q36",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 + 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "id": "q37",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 + 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "id": "q38",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "11 - 3 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q39",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "0 : 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": "q40",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "13 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": "q41",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "14 - 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q42",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 x 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "id": "q43",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "15 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q44",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "0 : 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": "q45",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "15 - 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q46",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "16 - 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q47",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "16 - 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q48",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 + 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "id": "q49",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "49 : 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q50",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "10 - 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "q51",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 x 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "63"
    },
    {
      "id": "q52",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "63 : 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q53",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "36 : 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q54",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "16 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q55",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "48 : 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q56",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "54 : 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q57",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "12 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": "q58",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "id": "q59",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "18 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "id": "q60",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 + 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "id": "q61",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 + 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "id": "q62",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 x 0 =",
      "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": "q63",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "15 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q64",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "48 : 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q65",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "14 - 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q66",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 x 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "48"
    },
    {
      "id": "q67",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "13 - 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": "q68",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "12 - 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q69",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 + 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "id": "q70",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "q71",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "id": "q72",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "10 + 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "id": "q73",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "13 - 4 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q74",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "48 : 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q75",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "10 - 3 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q76",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "13 - 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q77",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 + 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "id": "q78",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "11 - 2 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },

    {
      "id": "q79",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "14 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q80",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "12 - 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "q81",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 - 1 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q82",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "id": "q83",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 + 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "id": "q84",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 x 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "id": "q85",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "63 : 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q86",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "64 : 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q87",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "10 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": "q88",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 - 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": "q89",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "id": "q90",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 + 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "id": "q91",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "id": "q92",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "15 - 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q93",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "11 - 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q94",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 + 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "id": "q95",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "id": "q96",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "63 : 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q97",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 - 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "q98",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": "q99",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "9 + 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "id": "q100",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "81 : 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q101",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "id": "q102",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "12 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q103",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "12 - 4 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q104",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "7 + 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "id": "q105",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "54 : 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q106",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "13 - 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q107",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "14 - 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "id": "q108",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "14 + 10 =",
      "correct_answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "id": "q109",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "42 : 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q110",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "72 : 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "id": "q111",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "0 - 5 =",
      "correct_answer": "-5"
    },
    {
      "id": "q112",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "56 : 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "id": "q113",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "8 + 9 =",
      "correct_answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "id": "q114",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "6 - 0 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q115",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "17 + 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "id": "q116",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "48 : 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "id": "q117",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "0 - 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "-8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q118",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "56 : 7 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q119",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "48 : 6 =",
      "correct_answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "id": "q120",
      "type": "direct_input",
      "question_text": "56 : 8 =",
      "correct_answer": "7"
    }
  ]
}